I think overall that gives us confidence. But I would expect it to be a steady increase
in these initial months, not a hockey stick, simply because it does take time to get all
of that in place and then ultimately start bridging patients. We would expect then to
see an acceleration in 2027 as we then have the payers, a payer coverage in place, and
then we're well-suited to have a significant launch. It doesn't change our long-term outlook.
As we've guided, we think this can be a very large medicine in CSU alone. And then when
you add Sindhu on top, and then hopefully MS, hopefully HS, and then down the line additional
indications, food allergy, et cetera, we have a really exciting path ahead of us for
the medicine.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of James Quigley from Goldman Sachs. Please
go ahead.
Great. Thank you for taking my questions. I've got one on Deldesran in DM1. So as we
are heading into the data, what are you thinking would be a clinically meaningful impact on
video hand-opening time? And to what extent are the secondary endpoints even more important
here in interpreting the data into an overall benefit from a functionality perspective?
And then also any comments you have on the recent early data from Sarepta in the same
indication. So where do you think Deldesran will be differentiated relative to the emerging
competitors? Thank you.
Yes. I think we would be in a position to kind of comment on a series of questions.
I think we have a very specific video hand-opening time. But we do believe it's a well-understood
endpoint. And if we reach statistical significance, we think that would be an important milestone,
and all of our physician discussions would suggest that would be sufficient to warrant
broad use of the medicine. I think importantly as well, we're going to be looking at additional
functional outcomes such as the quantitative muscle testing and patient reporter-reported
outcomes, as well as the 10-meter walk-and-run test. I think all of that will help us to
improve our safety. And I think there is a lot of work going on to make sure that the
health care system is as robust as possible. I'm looking forward to seeing what we can do.
Okay. Thank you.
help us to further characterize the treatment effect. Now, when we look at some of the competitor
data, I think it's important to note it's quite early. And as we know in these medicines that
ultimately you need a relatively broad patients group because of the diversity of manifestations
of the disease. So I wouldn't want to over-interpret what we're seeing. Certainly,
it's exciting that there are many medicines coming forward to treat DM1 patients.
But we feel like because of the large data set that we have now, over 100 patients treated
across multiple disease states, 500 infusions, up to four years of multi-year exposure,